:
::
:::
::::
:::::
:::::[
:::::[G
:::::[GW
:::::[GWC
:::::[GWC]
:::::[GWC]:
:::::[GWC]::
:::::[GWC]:::
:::::[GWC]::::
:::::[GWC]:::::
We clawed, we chained,
our hearts in vain
We jumped
never asking why
We kissed,
I fell under your spell
A love no one could deny
Don’t you ever say I just walked away
I will always want you
I can’t live a lie
running for my life
I will always want you
I came in like a wrecking ball
I never hit so hard in love
All I wanted was to break your walls
All you ever did was break me
Yeah you
you wreck me
I put you high up in the sky
And now
you’re not coming down
It slowly turned,
you let me burn
And now
we’re ashes on the ground
Don’t you ever say
I just walked away
I will always want you
I can’t live a lie
running for my life
I will always want you
I came in like a wrecking ball
I never hit so hard in love
All I wanted was to break your walls
All you ever did was break me
I came in like a wrecking ball
Yeah, I just closed my eyes and swung
Left me crouching in a blaze and fall
All you ever did was break me
Yeah you
you wreck me
I never meant to start a war
I just wanted you to let me in
And instead of using force
I guess I should’ve let you in
I never meant to start a war
I just wanted you to let me in
I guess I should’ve let you in
Don’t you ever say I just walked away
I will always want you
I came in like a wrecking ball
I never hit so hard in love
All I wanted was to break your walls
All you ever did was break me
I came in like a wrecking ball
Yeah, I just closed my eyes and swung
Left me crouching in a blaze and fall
All you ever did was break me
Yeah you,
you wreck me
M
Me
Med
Medi
Media
Media &
Media & S
Media & Su
Media & Sub
Media & Subt
Media & Subti
Media & Subtit
Media & Subtitl
Media & Subtitle
:
::
Media & Subtitle
:::
::::
Media & Subtitle
:::::
:::::[
Media & Subtitle
:::::[G
:::::[GW
Media & Subtitle
:::::[GWC
:::::[GWC]
Media & Subtitle
:::::[GWC]:
:::::[GWC]::
Media & Subtitle
:::::[GWC]:::
:::::[GWC]::::
Media & Subtitle
:::::[GWC]:::::